Finding Aid for Peter Pollack papers, 1965-2009
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Project Files
  - Ann Arbor Projects
    - Textual Records
      - Mary Beth Doyle Park (Brown Park) Detention Basin
        - Correspondence and presentations, 5 folders (Box 13)
        - DEQ Permit 2005 (Box 13)
        - Mallet's Creek RFP (Box 14)
        - Meeting minutes 2006 (Box 14)
        - Project Manual (Box 14)
        - Proposal 2003, 2 folders (Box 14)
      - State Street Urban Design Project
        - Request for Qualifications (Box 14)
        - Construction Notes 2002-2003, 2 folders (Box 14)
        - Correspondence 2000-2003, 3 folders (Box 14)
        - Design Intent 2000-2001 (Box 14)
        - General 2001 (Box 14)
        - Plans and Drawings (Box 14)
        - State Street Area Project Pedestrian Improvement Plans November 2001 (Box 14)
        - South State Street Two-Way Traffic Study 2000 (Box 14)
        - South University Streetscape Improvements Proposal (Box 14)
      - University of Michigan
        - North Quad Site Improvements Technical Specifications 2009 (Box 14)
        - North Quad Working Files 2009 (Box 14)
        - Rackham Green Land Improvements Technical Specifications 2009 (Box 14)
    - Drawings and Plans
      - Allen Creek Greenway Taskforce -- Aerial Photographs and Overlays (Tube 42)
      - Ann Arbor Corridor Study
        - Aerial photographs and overlays (Tube 2)
        - Base Maps (Tube 2)
        - Sketches (Tube 2)
      - Broadway Street Shopping Area
        - Urban Design Plan January 10, 1981 (Map-case 1, Folder 1)
        - Richard Raab Parking Lot Schemes April 7, 1981 (Map-case 1, Folder 1)
        - Broadway Place Shopping Area Conceptual Sketches undated (Map-case 1, Folder 1)
        - Broadway Wall Project Slope Cross Sections September 8, 1983 (Map-case 1, Folder 1)
        - Kroger Parking Lot Options March 24, 1982 (Map-case 1, Folder 1)
        - Site Plan for Expansion of Broadway Kroger July 15, 1977 (Map-case 1, Folder 1)
        - Broadway Wall -- Grading and Slope Stabilization September 8, 1983 (Map-case 1, Folder 1)
        - Retaining Wall Extension May 23, 1984 (Map-case 1, Folder 1)
        - Raab Shopping Center Site Plan Options August 17, 1983 (Map-case 1, Folder 1)
        - Urban Design Plan January 10, 1981 (Tube 45)
        - Landscape Plan undated (Tube 45)
      - Cobblestone Farm 1985 (Map-case 1, Folder 1)
      - Downtown Development Authority (Map-case 1, Folder 2)
        - Maynard Street (Map-case 1, Folder 2)
        - Pedestrian Improvements Project
          - Detroit St/Farmers Market -- Misc. Plans and Drawings (Map-case 1, Folder 2)
          - Fourth Street -- Miscellaneous Plans and Drawings (Map-case 1, Folder 2)
          - Liberty Street (Map-case 1, Folder 2)
          - Liberty Street and Fourth Avenue (Map-case 1, Folder 2)
          - South University Pedestrian Way -- Plans and drawings (Map-case 1, Folder 2)
          - Detroit St/Farmer's Market -- Miscellaneous Plans and Drawings (Tube 5)
          - Fourth Avenue -- Miscellaneous Plans and Drawings (Tube 6)
          - Kerrytown Lighting April 1997 (Tube 7)
          - Phase I: Fall 1983, June 9, 1983 (Tube 7)
          - Phase I: Fall 1985, July 17, 1985 (Tube 7)
          - Phase II: Fall 1985 (Tube 8)
          - Phase II January 19, 1990 (Tube 8)
          - South University Pedestrian Way -- Miscellaneous Plans and drawings (Tube 9)
          - West Liberty Street (Tube 9)
          - Miscellaneous plans (Tube 9)
          - State Street Area Project Phase II Pedestrian Improvements -- Plans Issued for Bidding March 13, 2003 (Tube 10)
          - Urban Design Concept (Tube 10)
        - Fourth and Catherine Parking Lot -- Plans (Tube 3)
        - Liberty Plaza Improvements -- Issued for Bidding March 13, 2003 (Tube 4)
        - Miscellaneous Overlays (Tube 4)
        - North Corridor Campus Pathway (Tube 4)
        - State Street
          - Maynard and State Street Studies (Map-case 1, Folder 3)
          - State Street Pedestrian Alley (Map-case 1, Folder 3)
        - Tally Hall
          - Site Plan 1985 (Map-case 1, Folder 4)
          - Miscellaneous Plans (Map-case 1, Folder 4)
      - First Congregational Church
        - Miscellaneous Sketches and Courtyard Plans (Map-case 1, Folder 4)
      - Fuller-Glen
        - Early Concept Studies
          - Fuller/Glen Transit Project Preliminary Site Plans May 19, 1981 (Map-case 1, Folder 4)
          - Preliminary Bridge Railing Details May 19, 1981 (Map-case 1, Folder 4)
          - General Analysis Sketches October 26, 1979 (Map-case 1, Folder 4)
          - Conceptual Grading Plan May 1, 1981 (Map-case 1, Folder 4)
          - Early Site Studies (Map-case 1, Folder 4)
      - Fuller Road Wetland Mitigation (Map-case 1, Folder 4)
      - Fuller Road Projects
        - Plans
          - Fuller-Glen Project November 30, 1981 (Tube 11)
          - State Street to Glen Plan and Profile November 3, 1982 (Tube 11)
          - Fuller Rd/Oak Way Realignment May 19, 1993 (Tube 11)
        - Maps and Diagrams
          - Fuller Penetrator Bike Route Study October 21, 1975 (Tube 12)
          - Glen-Fuller Transit Project October 9, 1979 (Tube 12)
          - Fuller-Glen Final Alignment (Proposed) November 11, 1980 (Tube 12)
          - Fuller-Glen Shrub Bed Count September 22, 1983 (Tube 12)
          - Fuller Pool Entrance Revisions (Tube 12)
          - Fuller Rd Survey September 10, 1991 (Tube 12)
        - Fuller-Glenn Planting and Grading Studies (Tube 13)
        - Fuller-Glenn Public Hearing -- Overall Approach (Tube 13)
      - Furstenberg Park -- Miscellaneous Plans and Drawings 1991 (Map-case 1, Folder 5)
      - Furstenberg Park -- Miscellaneous Plans and Drawings 1991 (Tube 14)
      - Gandy Dancer
        - Schematic Site Plan March 1976 (Map-case 1, Folder 5)
        - Sketches (Map-case 1, Folder 5)
        - Plans June 24, 1976 (Tube 14)
        - Planting Plan May 1976 (Tube 14)
        - Schematic Site Plan March 1976 (Tube 14)
        - Sketches (Tube 14)
      - Huron-Division-Fifth St (Map-case 1, Folder 6)
        - Sketches and Drawings (Map-case 1, Folder 6)
        - Site Surveys (Tube 15)
        - Sketches (Tube 15)
        - Sketches and drawings (Tube 15)
      - Huron River Corridor Study (Map-case 1, Folder 6)
        - Master Plan Studies 1987 (Map-case 1, Folder 6)
        - Miscellaneous sketches (Map-case 1, Folder 6)
      - One-Way to Two-Way Signage Conversion Plans July 30, 2003 (Tube 15)
      - University of Michigan North Campus Hubbard-Hayward Street Proposed Realignment and Parking Lots Improvement Plan July 16, 1993 (Tube 15)
  - Herman Miller Projects
    The Herman Miller Projects (2 linear feet, 1 tube, 1 oversize folder) subseries documents various projects Pollack completed for Herman Miller, Inc. and their Zeeland and Holland, Michigan campuses. Materials include correspondence, permit applications, working files, sketches, and plans.
    - Textual Files
      - 104th Avenue, Street Improvement, 2 folders (Box 15)
      - Building B East (Box 15)
      - Building C-1 (Box 15)
      - Building F Entry (Box 15)
      - Burns
        - Post Ecological Prescription Burn Report and Landscape Management/Maintenance Observations (Box 15)
        - Prescribed Burn 2004 (Box 15)
        - SQA Burn (Box 15)
      - Correspondence (Box 15)
      - Design Yard (Box 15)
      - General Contacts 2003 (Box 15)
      - Greenhouse
        - General (Box 15)
        - LEED Greenhouse (Box 15)
        - Permanent Pavement (Box 15)
      - LEEDS Application (Box 15)
      - Main Site, B West (Box 15)
      - Main Site, Prescott B (Box 15)
      - MDC Planting (Box 15)
      - Phoenix Designs, 2 folders (Box 15)
      - Phoenix Designs Drawings 1996 (Box 15)
      - Planters (Box 15)
      - Site/Landscape Management and Maintenance
        - Program 1996 (Box 15)
        - Work session 1996 (Box 15)
      - SQA, 2 folders (Box 15)
      - Technical Specifications for MDC Pond ~ Shoreline Plant Conversion 2004 (Box 15)
      - Truck Parking (Box 15)
      - Van Wagoner Road (Box 15)
      - Zeeland Main Site (Box 15)
      - Zeeland Main Site plume (Box 15)
      - Zeeland Main Site Consumers Re-Alignment (Box 15)
      - Binders (many photographs included) (Box 16)
        - Powder Coat Technology facility (Box 16)
        - Miller SQA Facility (Box 16)
        - Phoenix Designs Project (Box 16)
        - Final site plan (Box 16)
    - Plans and Drawings
      - Photographs (Map-case 2, Folder 7)
      - Sketches (Map-case 2, Folder 7)
      - Zeeland Mainsite drawings (Tube 16)
      - Powder Coat Technology 1991 (Tube 16)
      - Dallas Schematic Site/Planting Plan (Tube 16)
      - SQA Greenhouse February 6, 2001 (Tube 16)
      - Phase 1 Construction 1995 (Tube 16)
      - New Phase 1 Plant and Offices January 17, 1995 (Tube 16)
      - Miscellaneous (Tube 16)
  - Pfizer Campus Projects
    The Pfizer Campus Projects (4.5 linear feet, 22 tubes, 5 oversize folders) subseries includes correspondence, minutes, permit applications, study results, plans, drawings, and sketches related to the Warner-Lambert, Parke-Davis, and Pfizer in Ann Arbor. There is a small amount of material related to the Kalamazoo campus as well. Major projects profiled include the Parke-Davis master plan, the 2800 Plymouth Road Facility, Pfizer's Planned Unit Development (PUD), and Stormwater Wetlands Management.
    - Textual Files
      - Parke-Davis/Warner Lambert
        - Master Plan
          - Relocation Master Plan 1984 (Box 17)
          - Master Plan 1984 (Box 17)
          - Master Plan 1985 (Box 17)
          - Master Plan 1989-1990 (Box 17)
          - Master Plan Update 1996 (Box 17)
          - Master Plan with Heidi
            - Master Plan 1996-1997 (Box 17)
            - Background Materials (Box 17)
            - Correspondence File 1996, 2 folders (Box 17)
          - Master Plan III 2000 (Box 17)
          - Building 20 Addition 1998 (Box 17)
          - Documentation 1997 (Box 17)
          - Graphics (Box 17)
          - Working Session 1998 (Box 17)
          - Master Site Plan/Strategic 7 Year Plan 1997 (Box 17)
          - Master Plan Report 1997, 2 folders (Box 17)
        - 2800 Plymouth Road Facility
          - Alternate (Box 17)
          - Building 26 Pre-Clinical Laboratory 1999 (Box 17)
          - Building 26 Site Plan 2000 (Box 17)
          - Cafeteria Conference Center Plan 1998 (Box 17)
          - Childcare Center 1998 (Box 17)
          - FAR Calculations 1999 (Box 17)
          - Landscape Maintenance Proposal Form draft 1990 (Box 17)
          - Materials Handling Center and Conference Cafeteria Center 1998 (Box 17)
          - Materials Handling Center Plan 1998 (Box 17)
          - Materials Handling Center Specs 1998 (Box 17)
          - Power House Addition 1993 (Box 17)
          - Power House Addition/South Parking Lot Site Plan 1993 (Box 17)
          - Project Management and Communication 1999 (Box 17)
          - Site Plan 1998 (Box 17)
        - 2800 Plymouth Road Facility
          - South 15 Acres
            - New Site Development 1993 (Box 17)
            - Project Book
              - Construction Meetings 1993-1995 (Box 17)
              - Submittals 1993-1994 (Box 17)
              - Addendum 1993-1994 (Box 17)
              - Pay Estimates 1993-1994 (Box 17)
              - Miscellaneous 1993-1994 (Box 17)
          - Technical Development Facility
            - General 1998 (Box 18)
            - Submittal Originals 1996-1999 (Box 18)
            - Site Plan 1998-2005, 2 folders (Box 18)
            - Site Work -- Issued for Construction 1998 (Box 18)
          - Preliminary Detention Study November 1, 1990 (Box 18)
          - Re-Zoning Application September 14, 1992 (Box 18)
          - Traffic Study 1990 (Box 18)
      - Pfizer
        - Master Plan/Planned Unit Development (PUD)
          - Ann Arbor Planning Department Reports 1992-2001 (Box 18)
          - Baxter Road Entrance and Guard Kiosk Plans 2005 (Box 18)
          - Building 10 Executive Courtyard 2003 (Box 18)
          - Building 28 Plans 2006 (Box 18)
          - Building 35 Plans 2005 (Box 18)
          - Buildings 85 and 75 2003 (Box 18)
          - Campus Enhancements III 2005 (Box 18)
          - Chronological File
            - January-October, 2001 (Box 18)
            - September-October, 2001 (Box 18)
            - November-December, 2001 (Box 18)
            - January-February, 2002 (Box 18)
            - August-October, 2002 (Box 18)
            - November-December, 2002 (Box 18)
            - January 2003 (Box 18)
          - cGMP Warehouse Plans 2006 (Box 18)
          - Community Context and Redevelopment Opportunities 2007 (Box 18)
          - Concept Master Plan sketches 2001 (Box 18)
          - Engineering 2000 (Box 18)
          - Global Facilities Management Information Document 2002 (Box 18)
          - Guard Kiosk and Site Improvements 2004 (Box 18)
          - Informational 2000-2002 (Box 18)
          - Land and Water Management -- Wetland Inventory 2000 (Box 18)
          - Lawn Conversion -- Phase IV 2005 (Box 18)
          - Lighting 2000 (Box 18)
          - Master Plan Edits 2003 (Box 18)
          - Master Planning 2001-2003, 3 folders (Box 18)
          - Master Plan Meetings 2001-2003 (Box 19)
          - Master Plan Overlays 2002 (Box 19)
          - Master Plan Proposals 2000-2002 (Box 19)
          - Natural Features
            - 55 Acre Site Natural Features Inventory 2001 (Box 19)
            - Landmark Tree Survey 2001 (Box 19)
            - Natural Features 2002 (Box 19)
            - Natural Features Data 2002 (Box 19)
            - Natural Features Inventory 2002 (Box 19)
            - Veridian Botanical Inventory and Landmark Tree Survey 2002 (Box 19)
          - Parking 2008 (Box 19)
          - Patrick Judd File 2001-2002 (Box 19)
          - Plans and Graphics 2002 (Box 19)
          - Prairie Conversion -- Phase II 2003 (Box 19)
          - Project Review Coordination 1999 (Box 19)
          - Sanitary Sewer Analysis 2001 (Box 19)
          - Scanned Photos undated (Box 19)
          - Site Design Standards 2002 (Box 19)
          - Site Options Study 2001 (Box 19)
          - Site Photographs (Box 19)
          - Site Planning and Design Team Meeting 2004 (Box 19)
          - Site Plans for Parking Structure and Wetlands Use Permit 2000 (Box 19)
          - Strategic Facilities Plan 2004 (Box 19)
          - Strategic Site Plan and Master Plan Review 2003 (Box 19)
          - Strategic Site Plans 2000-2005, 5 folders (Box 19)
          - Zoning
            - Rezoning and Area Plan 2002 (Box 19)
            - Zoning 2001-2002 (Box 19)
            - Zoning Petition 2001 (Box 19)
        - Coordination Meeting 2003 (Box 19)
        - Coordination Meeting Minutes 1998-2002, 3 folders (Box 19)
        - Coordination Meeting Minutes 1998-2002, 2 folders (Box 20)
        - Miller's Creek
          - Breakfast and Open House 2003 (Box 20)
          - Correspondence 2001-2003, 2 folders (Box 20)
          - Crossing Options 2004 (Box 20)
          - Grant Application 2005-2006 (Box 20)
          - Watershed Improvement Plan 2003 (Box 20)
        - Site Acquisition 2001 (Box 20)
        - Stormwater Wetlands Management
          - Building 14 Courtyard 2000 (Box 20)
          - Detention Basin 3 2001-2002 (Box 20)
          - Land and Water Management Master Plan
            - DEQ Permit Correspondence 2000 (Box 20)
            - Site Improvement 2000 (Box 20)
            - Specifications 2000 (Box 20)
          - Photographs (Box 20)
          - Stormwater Management Master Plan
            - Bid Period 2000 (Box 20)
            - Calculations 2000 (Box 20)
            - Chronological File
              - September-December, 1999 (Box 20)
              - January-May, 2000 (Box 20)
              - June-July, 2000 (Box 20)
              - March 2001 (Box 20)
          - Storm Water Management Study 2001 (Box 20)
          - Stormwater Research Introduction 2002 (Box 20)
          - Stormwater Update 1984-1999 (Box 20)
          - Wetland Annual Monitoring Report 2003 (Box 21)
          - Wetland Investigation and Delineation 2001 (Box 21)
          - Wetland Monitoring -- Basin 3 2001-2002 (Box 21)
          - Wetland Use Permit 2000 (Box 21)
    - Drawings and Plans
      - Parke-Davis/Warner-Lambert
        - Building 10 Courtyard-Preliminary Planting Plan August 14, 1992 (Map-case 2, Folder 8)
        - Child Care Center
          - Miscellaneous sketches 1998 (Map-case 2, Folder 8)
          - Playground Concept Sketch March 31, 1999 (Map-case 2, Folder 8)
        - The Courtyard
          - Existing Conditions January 26, 1987 (Map-case 2, Folder 8)
          - Sketch Options January 1987 (Map-case 2, Folder 8)
          - Courtyard Planting Plan March 4, 1987 (Map-case 2, Folder 8)
          - Miscellaneous sketches (Map-case 2, Folder 8)
        - Entry Gate and Signage
          - Miscellaneous Plans and Drawings 1992 (Map-case 2, Folder 9)
          - Signage sketches undated (Map-case 2, Folder 9)
        - Master Plans Studies 1992-1993 (Map-case 2, Folder 9)
        - North Entrance Court
          - Miscellaneous sketches (Map-case 2, Folder 9)
        - Parking Deck-Miscellaneous sketches and plans (Map-case 2, Folder 10)
        - Switch Box Buffer-Concept Sketches June 21, 1999 (Map-case 2, Folder 10)
        - Toxicology Building-Planting Plans May 8, 1985 (Map-case 2, Folder 10)
        - Miscellaneous Plans (Map-case 2, Folder 10)
        - Administration Support Facility Plans September 8, 2000 (Tube 17)
        - Building 26
          - Building 23 & 26 Phase II Construction Drawings June 9, 2000 (Tube 17)
          - Building 26 Phase II Construction Drawings August 1, 2000 (Tube 17)
          - Building 26, Pre-Clinical Laboratory, and Parking Site Improvement Plans December 4, 2002 (Tube 18)
          - Miscellaneous Sketches (Tube 18)
        - Building 35 Addition September 2, 2004 (Tube 18)
        - Building PC-1 Preliminary Planting Plan Options undated (Tube 18)
        - Child Care Center-Plans Issued for Bidding June 1, 1999 (Tube 19)
        - Clinical Research Building 16
          - General Trades September 4, 1990 (Tube 19)
          - Site and Foundation Package April 19, 1990 (Tube 20)
        - Cooling Towers -- Issued for Construction June 2, 1997 (Tube 20)
        - Entry Gate and Signage
          - Miscellaneous Plans and Drawings 1992 (Tube 21)
          - Signage sketches undated (Tube 21)
        - Fitness Trail
          - Seed Mix Layout Modifications May 1989 (Tube 21)
          - Preliminary Parcour Layout August 1988 (Tube 21)
          - Fitness Trail Layout Record November 2, 1988 (Tube 21)
        - Future Development Plan Options undated (Tube 21)
        - Granite Sculpture Site Improvements
          - Issued for Owner's Review April 16, 2002 (Tube 21)
          - Issued for Construction August 12, 2002 (Tube 21)
        - Huron Parkway Connector Tunnel -- Construction Issue, Site Work December 14, 2000 (Tube 22)
        - Land and Water Management
          - Plans Issued for Construction May 17, 2000 (Tube 22)
          - Re-Application for Inland Lakes and Stream Permit May 12, 2000 (Tube 22)
        - Master Plans Studies 1992-1993 (Tube 23)
        - Materials Handling Center and Cafeteria Conference Center Site Improvement Plans March 22, 1999 (Tube 23)
        - New Site Development: South 15 Acres
          - Plans Issued for Construction September 8, 1993 (Tube 23)
        - North Entrance Court
          - Conclusion of Design Development Plans March 9, 2001 (Tube 23)
          - Miscellaneous Plans 2001 (Tube 24)
          - Program/Character Discussion Diagrams October 2000 (Tube 24)
        - North Parking Addition July 11, 1997 (Tube 24)
        - North Parking Lot Area and Southwest Trucking Dock July 11, 1989 (Tube 24)
        - Parking Deck
          - Phase II Minor Modification February 1990 (Tube 25)
          - Issued for Construction November 29, 1990 (Tube 25)
        - Parking Lots B, C, and D Relocation and Minor Building Additions July 19, 1999 (Tube 25)
        - Power House Addition, South Parking Lot, and Entry Drive (Tube 26)
          - Appendix A June 2, 1993 (Tube 26)
          - Wetland Permit Application May 27, 1993 (Tube 26)
          - Administrative Amendment April 4, 1994 (Tube 26)
          - As-Built Record March 7, 1995 (Tube 26)
          - Preliminary Sketch Landscape Plan April 29, 1993 (Tube 26)
        - Southern Parking Area Earthwork and Reforestation February 26, 1990 (Tube 27)
        - Southwest Entry Schematic Designs June 9, 2004 (Tube 27)
        - Storm Sewer Tie-In Plans 1991 (Tube 27)
        - Storm Water Management Master Plan 2000 (Tube 27)
        - Switch Box Buffer
          - Plans Issued for Bidding August 1, 1999 (Tube 27)
        - Technical Development Facility (Tube 28)
          - Plans Issued for Construction August 3, 1999 (Tube 28)
          - Administrative Amendment October 18, 2005 (Tube 28)
          - Site Capacity Diagram (Tube 28)
        - Temporary Modular Addition to Building 50 December 17, 1998 (Tube 28)
        - Temporary Modular Office Addition (Tube 29)
          - Plans Issued for Bidding April 13, 1998 (Tube 29)
          - Plan Submitted for Administrative Amendment April 1, 1998 (Tube 29)
        - Temporary Parking Relocation -- Issued for Construction May 9, 2000 (Tube 29)
        - Toxicology Building
          - Proposed Planting Plans April 1985 (Tube 29)
          - Planting Plans May 8, 1985 (Tube 29)
        - Tree Area Removal and Relocation Proposals April 1990 (Tube 29)
        - The Pond and Building Edge
          - Preliminary Sketch Options January 1987 (Tube 30)
          - Final Preliminary Plan February 10, 1987 (Tube 30)
          - Planting Plan March 4, 1987 (Tube 30)
        - University of Michigan
          - Preliminary Grading Plan November 1990 (Tube 30)
          - Tree Relocation November 1990 (Tube 30)
          - Regrading and Soil Stabilization Plan July 1992 (Tube 30)
        - Miscellaneous Plans and Drawings (Tube 30)
      - Pfizer
        - 1600 Site Plan Schematics, April 2006 (Map-case 2, Folder 11)
        - Building 10Executive Courtyard Sketches 2003 (Map-case 2, Folder 11)
        - Building 28 Loading Dock Renovation and South End Distribution -- Sketches 2006 (Map-case 2, Folder 11)
        - Campus Green and Entrance Plaza July 2000 (Map-case 2, Folder 11)
        - Development Office Building Site Influences November 26, 2003 (Map-case 2, Folder 11)
        - ERIN Walks and Planting Schematic February 18, 1993 (Map-case 2, Folder 11)
        - Kalamazoo Campus
          - Final Schematic Options September 2008 (Map-case 2, Folder 11)
          - Lot 1 Options August 2008 (Map-case 2, Folder 11)
          - Rough Grading Options December 2005 (Map-case 2, Folder 11)
          - Sketches (Map-case 2, Folder 12)
          - Studies 2000 (Map-case 2, Folder 12)
        - Miller's Crossing
          - Sketches April 23, 2003 (Map-case 2, Folder 12)
          - Evaluation Criteria April 18, 2003 (Map-case 2, Folder 12)
        - Site Options Study Sketches 2001 (Map-case 2, Folder 12)
        - Miscellaneous Plans and Drawings (Map-case 2, Folder 12)
        - Area Plan undated (Tube 31)
        - Baxter Road Entrance and Guard Kiosk -- Issued for 100% Final Review September 9, 2005 (Tube 31)
        - Building 10/20 Courtyard-Plans Issued for Bidding, March 30, 2001 (Tube 32)
        - Building 20 -- Stair Tower Addition, Submitted for Administrative Amendment February 5, 2004 (Tube 32)
        - Building 28 Loading Dock Renovation and South End Distribution -- Submitted for PUD Site Plan Administrative Amendment March 10, 2006 (Tube 32)
        - Building 35